<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Garv&#039;s Brain 🧠</title>
      <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Garv&#039;s Brain 🧠</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Build a Successful Student Club</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/Build-a-Successful-Student-Club</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/Build-a-Successful-Student-Club</guid>
    <description> make a mission statement create a plan for where we’re going Attracting and Retaining Members § Open doors Be welcoming to all students who are interested in your club Offer perks Have attractive perks such as food, exclusive events, and leadership roles to encourage people to join.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>To-Do</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/To-Do</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/To-Do</guid>
    <description>group by status.type group by function task.tags short mode.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>🏠 Home</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/</guid>
    <description>Hi! Welcome to my notes :) Currently you can explore my School Subjects or University Applications. School Subjects Currently I’m doing English Language, Literature, Physics, Algorithmics, Specialist Maths and Maths Methods for VCE! .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Fri October 27th 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Fri-October-27th-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Fri-October-27th-2023</guid>
    <description>Problem with Kahoot: If you are in a university with own server and computer, limitation is internet, there would be times there will be lag, and that lag would create a difference in how fast a person would respond Local LAN version without using the internet at all WLAN router is accessible wireless bluetooth devices, wireless lan, seperate ip wireless lan device .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mon August 14th 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Mon-August-14th-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Mon-August-14th-2023</guid>
    <description> Uniform - scenario question: you are on the committee, and you have a job to encourage more students to wear their uniform with pride. How could you do this? I think the school uniform looks wonderful, and with the new uniform being able to mix and match makes it much more convenient, which increases school pride I think allowing for variation was key and I can see the benefit around me Could possibly allow and maybe even encourage accessories that adhere to the school environment and vision to let students get creative.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mon July 17th 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Mon-July-17th-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Mon-July-17th-2023</guid>
    <description>I’m in the city today! I got invited to Tildes which is really cool and I’ve been having some fun with that. Right now I’m in the Melbourne Connect building and I’m meeting with Prof Alistair Moffat.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mon July 24th 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Mon-July-24th-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Mon-July-24th-2023</guid>
    <description>Today is much better than the weekend, twas very depressing. Keep working on Algorithmics SAT#algo algo .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Sat July 8th 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Sat-July-8th-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Sat-July-8th-2023</guid>
    <description>Starting to use Daily Notes! § Setup Obsidian how I like Setup Obsidian how I like .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Sun July 30th 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Sun-July-30th-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Sun-July-30th-2023</guid>
    <description>School leadership! Personal brand is about how I genuinely find it really fun and enjoyable to help other people and school leadership is an opportunity to make a wider impact and have others realise their abilities talk about student mental health connection with other campuses connection with many facets of the school, bring together communities year levels working more with each other, after covid only gotten to know own year level, personally only gotten much closer to year level below me this year, could try to have more of that, maybe a buddy system with year 12s and 7s .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Thu November 23rd 2023</title>
    <link>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Thu-November-23rd-2023</link>
    <guid>https://garv-shah.github.io/brain/notes/Daily-Notes/Thu-November-23rd-2023</guid>
    <description>Spec exam today! Prove that Var(aX)=a2Var(X).</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>